Reinforcements will be coming soon, as well.
Give up, leave the Hundreds
you've taken, and surrender.
Rain?
Nee-chan. Nakri.
It seems luck is on our side.
Nee-chan! Nakri!
Trace On.
Instead of attacking me,
they went after my cannons?
That won't work!
Your power is completely
reduced in this rain!
Then take this!
Too slow!
I'll finish you off.
Dragon Type
What?
Damn it.
That's not going to work.
You can't escape my Everlasting.
Erica.
President, are you okay?
Kisaragi Hayato.
I'm here, too.
Me three.
There's nothing you can do now.
Surrender.
You've got to be kidding me!
We've always been fighting our way out
of this exact situation.
This ain't nearly enough to make us give up!
Trace On.
Let me take care of this.
The guy from before, huh?
If you don't let go of your weapons,
you won't be able to move from there.
You're going to end up on a stake.
Then finish me off now!
As you wish.
Nakri...
Looks like this is over.
Trace O...
Looks like you can't replicate
the things you see immediately.
Also...
I imagine you won't be replicating much
if I stab out that eye of yours.
You're going to destroy my eye?
Why do you have your eyes?
To hurt people?
Or is it...
...to see this beautiful world of ours?
Beautiful, my ass! Don't make me laugh!
The only thing we've ever seen is despair!
The strong oppress the weak,
and control them!
That's the kind of hellish world
we've lived through!
And we're going to...
...change this world!
And become truly free!
Don't try to get in our way!
Don't get in our way! Don't get in our way!
Don't get in our way!
Wh-What is this?
Don't dillydally! Keep moving!
What are you doing there?
Get back to your post!
Nesat!
Are you okay?
At this rate, she'll lose her sight.
No way...
But I can bestow new light...
And power.
Power?
Power to make you free.
Are these his memories?
Do you have a reason to fight?
A reason to win?!
I do!
The Hundred...
This power can bring
a smile to everyone's faces!
If I want to protect their smiles...
If I want to protect everyone I care about,
I can't lose!
Losing is not an option!
Full-body armament?
I have to make this world a better place!
A place where no one gets hurt,
and everyone can smile!
That is why...
...I fight!
That's impossible!
I'm sure it's possible as long as
someone truly desires it!
And that is my desire!
I want a world where no one
gets hurt... a happy one!
Krovanh!
Damn it...
I'm not done yet...
I can still fight!
I have to fight!
He's being consumed by his Variant power...
Stop!
If you keep using your Variant power,
your body will...
Like I care.
Wh-What's that?
Is it a Savage?
No way...
That's where Squad B is!
This is bad!
We need to do something!
I know, but...
They're still...
Hundred...
This is a trade.
Let's call a ceasefire.
I'll defeat that Savage for you.
What was that?
In exchange,
we'll take its core.
Stop it!
If you use any more of your power...
Shut up!
We need it!
We need that core!
Take this!
What?!
A wide-area barrier!
If we can bring this back,
we'll be able to be truly free!
And the three of us...
Krovanh, stop it!
It's right here, but why...
Why can't I get to it?!
Why?! Why?!
Why is it?!
Krovanh!
Are you okay?
Why did you save me?
Didn't I tell you?
I want to make a world
where no one gets hurt.
Then please...
I don't care about what happens to me.
Help Nee-chan and Nakri...
Not so fast!
Are the other squads attacking?
President, if both of us fire at once,
we might be able to destroy that barrier.
Let's try it.
Hold on, Claire-sama.
Three's better than two.
And four's better than three.
Let's get all of the Slayers on this mountain
capable of long-range fire
to fire at the same time.
And how will we get them to do that?
Right now...
Oh yeah, our transmissions...
You guys are the ones jamming
our transmissions, right?
Where is the jamming device?
If we want to take out that Savage,
we have to communicate
with the other squads.
Please help us.
Comms are back up.
You have my thanks.
Erica, get me the Little Garden.
Right.
Hey, Claire.
It seems like an unexpected situation
is occurring over there.
Professor Charlotte,
there's something we'd like you
to calculate immediately.
Here's what LiZA came up with.
If all of the long-range Slayers there
fire at the same time,
that barrier can be destroyed.
To all Slayers:
You heard that, didn't you?
Yeah.
We're going to take out that Savage, huh?
I'll lend a hand.
Claire, we've got the green light
from joint mission command.
Then I,
the queen of the Little Garden,
shall take command of this mission.
Right!
Kisaragi Hayato,
you deal the finishing blow.
Right!
Everyone, prepare to fire!
Roger that!
We're detecting a large amount of
energy from the Savage!
This is bad!
It's not working...?
Why?
Not enough firepower.
Looks like some Slayers couldn't attack because
the Savage got them right beforehand.
So we can't do anything...
There is one thing.
Really, Char?
I don't really want to suggest it,
but LiZA recommends that...
Kisaragi Hayato share his Variant power
with you, Claire Harvey.
Huh? W-Wait...
Wouldn't that mean...
Yes.
Kisaragi Hayato and Claire Harvey
would have to kiss.
What?!
No! That's not happening!
Never in a million years!
Y-Yeah! The president
needs to remain pure.
What's the big deal?
That would mean... you'd inject the
Variant virus into my body, right?
But there is a risk involved.
Doing this will help temporarily,
but there's no telling what long-term
effects it could have on your body.
But I'll have to do it.
Right now,
taking that Savage out comes first.
Yeah, but...
You just can't!
The rest is up to you, Kisaragi Hayato-kun.
K-Kisaragi Hayato.
D-Do you not want to... k-kiss me?
U-Uh...
That's not the problem.
Detecting another high energy burst
from the Savage!
It's going to attack! Please hurry!
Fine, I get it!
Just get it over with already!
I-I'm sorry, President!
There's no reason for you to apologize.
There's something warm entering my body...
This is Kisaragi Hayato's...
I feel myself overflowing with power.
Everyone, please.
Let's do this one more time.
Sure.
Roger that, queen.
I'm ready anytime.
All Slayers are charging.
Charging complete!
3, 2, 1...
Fire!
I'm ending this here!
We did it!
Hayato!
Finish it off!
Don't lose yourself.
I can do this, too!
I can't lose to myself!
No matter what!
Hayato!
Emilia-sama!
Hayato, where are you?!
Hayato!
Hayato! Hayato!
Hayato...
The injured Slayers are recovering steadily.
That's great.
But it would be difficult for us to
participate in the following mission...
Let's leave the rest up to the groups
from the various countries.
Um... Claire-sama...
About that three hunters...
I don't understand what
Judar-sama is trying to do.
Why are we moving them
to the Little Garden?
That might end up being a risk
to the Little Garden.
I feel the same way you do.
Just what are you planning,
Onii-sama?
The moon is wonderful.
It wanes and waxes.
No problems anymore.
He's out of danger.
Hayato...
As long as the Variant virus remains stable,
I'm sure he'll wake up soon.
Take care of him.
Sorry for making you push yourself, Hayato.
Wake up soon.
Emile-san?
Hey, what are you doing?
Well, I, uh...
R-Right. There was something in his eyes...
Isn't he asleep?
I-It looked like
you were kissing him to me.
O-Of course not!
Why would Hayato and I kiss?
Of course you wouldn't. You're both boys.
Yeah.
Something's fishy.
Hayato!
Nii-san!
Karen...
Sakura...
Emile's here, too.
What a relief...
Good morning, Hayato.
You did well.
So Krovanh and the others
aren't coming back, huh?
Well, it matters not.
There are no further hindrances to my plan.
School Festa